elements4health.com 2015-03-20

# Privacy Policy

Elements4Health recognizes that your privacy and the protection of your personal information is important to you and is committed to protecting your privacy. The privacy policy described below applies to the site and services offered by Elements4Health.

BY USING THIS SITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS POLICY.

This policy was last modified in November 2010.

Elements4Health provides you with original articles about a variety of health topics.

What information is collected by Elements4Health:

You may use Elements4Healthâ€™s services anonymously and we will not collect any personal information about you.

What information is collected by Elements4Health via technology:

Elements4Health notes and saves information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, IP address, and IP location with each query.

Elements4Health uses cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this or other websites you visit.  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

In particular, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Googleâ€™s use of the DoubleClick DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on your visits to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Privacy of Minors:

The Elements4Health services are not intended to be used by minors under the age of 13 and Elements4Health does not intentionally collect or maintain information from those visitors and users of the services who are under the age of 13.

When your information may be disclosed:

Elements4Health may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the requirements of the law or comply with legal process served on Elements4Health or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Elements4Health; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect personal safety of users of Elements4Health, its websites, or the public.

Updates to this privacy policy:

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the â€˜last updatedâ€™ date at the top of the Privacy Policy. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

Sale of assets:

In the unlikely event that Elements4Health or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

Terms of use:

Please also visit our Terms of Use section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

Third party links:

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).

Questions and feedback:

Elements4Health welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that Elements4Health has not adhered to this Policy, please contact us by using our online feedback form and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
